#### Contact

D-178 street no 8 laxmi nagar delhi 110092 8506932001 (Mobile) er.mohit.gupta1993@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/mohit-gupta-670587157 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Data Modeling Statistical Data Analysis Data Analysis

# Mohit Gupta

Data Analyst | Data Engineer | Data Scientist East Delhi

### Summary

Experienced Data Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the business consulting environment in the Pharmaceutical and Telecom domain. Skilled in SQL, VBA, Python, SAS, Linux, Microsoft Excel, SalesForce Effectiveness, Business Consulting, and Employee Engagement.

## Experience

Walmart Labs
Software Engineer
August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Gurgaon, Haryana, India

WNS Global Services
Data Analyst
May 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 4 months)

Infozech Software Private Limited Software Developer April 2015 - May 2017 (2 years 2 months) Delhi, India

#### Education

Noida Institute of Engineering & Technology
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)

Bal Bhavan Public School High school, Physics · (2007 - 2011)